ivyexec.com 2018-08-29

# Privacy Policy

Ivy Exec is committed to respecting the privacy of our users and providing a safe and secure experience for all professionals and employers. The Ivy Exec Websites and all related mobile applications and other interactive properties and services (collectively, the “Websites”) are owned, operated and distributed by Ivy Exec, Inc., a Delaware corporation (referred to in this Privacy Policy as ”Ivy Exec” or “we” and through similar words such as “us,” “our,” etc.). This Privacy Policy outlines the personal data that Ivy Exec may collect, how Ivy Exec uses and safeguards that data, and with whom we may share it. This Privacy Policy is intended to provide notice to individuals regarding personal data in an effort to be compliant with the data privacy laws and regulations of the jurisdictions in which Ivy Exec operates.

By using our Websites or submitting personal data to Ivy Exec by any other means, you acknowledge that you understand and agree to be bound by this Privacy Policy, and agree that Ivy Exec may collect, process, transfer, use and disclose your personal data as described in this Policy. Further, by accessing any part of the Websites, you are agreeing to the terms and conditions of our Terms of Use (the “Terms of Use”). If at any time you wish to withdraw your consent for processing your personal data, you may contact Ivy Exec as described in this Privacy Policy.

If you do not agree to any of these terms, you should not use the Websites. This Privacy Policy applies to all users, including both users who are simply viewing content available via the Websites and users who have subscribed for services and/or are contributors of content via the Websites.

### Personal Data Collected

During your use of the Ivy Exec Websites and services, personal data may be collected and processed by Ivy Exec. The data you submit to us may vary based on the type of employment sought or information available on your CV. You may affirmatively provide Ivy Exec with certain personal data including, but not limited to:

  * Contact Information (name, home address, home phone number, personal email);
  * Employment history;
  * Education;
  * Experience, licensure, and technical skills;
  * Similar information contained on your resume.

In addition, through your use of the website, we store such information as:

  * Jobs you've applied to;
  * Jobs you've viewed;
  * And similar information.

You control the information provided to us, and we do no collect information outside of the information that you submit via the Ivy Exec Websites. In addition to information about yourself, you will have the option to provide information about friends that may be interested in our service, such as a friend’s email address.

### Our Use of Personal Data

The personal contact information (i.e. street address, phone number, email address) that you provide in this registration process is confidential. We will use your personal data for internal purposes only and will never sell your personal data with any third parties. Should you fill out a registration form, the amount of information you choose to keep confidential is entirely up to your discretion. You may enter as much or as little information as you choose. All information posted will only be viewable by registered user on the Websites. All employers and professionals are screened before they are given access to the database.

We use First Data to provide credit card processing services on our Websites. For more information on First Data's privacy policy, [click here.](https://www.firstdata.com/en_us/privacy.html)

If you choose to use our invitation service to tell a friend about our Websites, we will ask you for information needed to send the invitation, such as your friend's email address. If you choose to import your friend's information, we will not store your password after importing your friend's information. We will send your friend an email in your name inviting him or her to visit the Websites and may send up to three reminders to them. Your friend may contact us at [professionals@ivyexec.com](mailto:professionals@ivyexec.com) to request that we remove this information from our database.

We may use your email address, phone number or other personally identifiable information to send commercial or marketing messages if you have not opted out from receiving these communications from us. We also may use your email address, phone number and other personally identifiable information for non-marketing or administrative purposes (such as notifying you of major service changes or for customer service purposes). You cannot opt out of receiving communications for non-marketing or administrative purposes.

### Disclosure of Personal Data

We do not sell your personal data to third parties - ever. Although we may disclose information about the use of our Websites, that information does not contain Personal Data. Generally, we do not disclose personal data to third parties. However, we may share personal data with our contractors and service providers in order to maintain, enhance, or add to the functionality of the Websites. If Ivy Exec becomes part of another organization, that organization will possess the personal data collected by IvyExec.com and it will assume the rights and obligations regarding your personal data as described in this Privacy Policy.

We use other third parties to provide Web analytics on the Websites. When you sign up for the Websites, we will share aggregate click data as necessary for the third party to provide that service. These third parties are prohibited from using your personally identifiable information for any other purpose.

### Internet Protocol Address

Like most Websites, we collect Internet Protocol ("IP") address from all visitors to the Websites. An IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer when you use the Internet. We use IP addresses to help diagnose problems with our server, administer the Websites, analyze trends, track users' movement, gather broad demographic information for aggregate use in order for us to improve the Websites, and deliver customized, personalized content.

### Cookies, Web Beacons and Similar Tools

When you access the Websites, we may send one or more “cookies” to your computer. A "cookie" is a small line of text that is stored with your browser, which we use to help provide better service to you. Your browser has options to accept, reject or provide you with notice when a cookie is sent. We may use cookies for many purposes, including (without limitation) to save information so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit the Websites, and to deliver content (which may include third party advertisements) specific to your interests. In addition, we may employ "clear GIFs" (a.k.a. Web Beacons) and similar tools, which are used to track usage patterns anonymously (i.e., in a non-personally-identifiable manner). In addition, we may also use these tools in HTML-based emails sent to users to track which emails are opened by recipients.

### EU Privacy Rights

If you are in the European Union (EU), the General Data Protection Regulation grants you certain rights under the law. In particular, the right to access, correct, or delete the personal data Ivy Exec holds about you. Ivy Exec will retain your data for the length of time you engage with our services until you request deletion of such personal data.

Upon request, Ivy Exec will grant individuals reasonable access to personal data that it holds about them. In addition, Ivy Exec will take reasonable steps to permit individuals to correct, amend, or delete information it holds about them. Ivy Exec also relies upon each individual to assist in providing accurate updates of his or her personal data. In order to access, correct, amend, or delete the personal data Ivy Exec holds about an individual, the individual should contact.

If you have a comment, question, or complaint about how Ivy Exec is handling your personal data, we hope that you contact us in order to allow us to resolve the matter. In addition, individuals located in the EU may submit a complaint regarding the processing of their personal data to the EU data protection authorities (DPAs). The following link may assist you in finding the appropriate DPA: http://ec.europa.eu/justice/data-protection/bodies/authorities/index_en.htm.

### International Data Transfer

For individuals in Switzerland, the EU, Asia, or any other region with laws or regulations governing personal data collection, use, and disclosure, that differ from United States laws, please note that Ivy Exec is a US based company. If you use the Websites, all information, including personal information, will be transferred to Ivy Exec (including third parties to which data was disclosed as described above) in the United States and information made available through the Websites may be viewed by individuals located anywhere in the world. The Websites are hosted in the United States and are primarily intended for and directed to users in the United States. Please be advised that through your continued use of the Websites, which is governed by U.S. law, this Privacy Policy, and our Terms of Use, you consent to the transfer of your personal data to the United States.

### Other Websites

Ivy Exec contains links to other Websites over which we have no control and bear no responsibility. We are not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of other Websites to which you choose to link from our Websites. Often these sites require you to enter your personal data as you apply for a job directly with the hiring company. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of those other Websites so you can understand how they collect, use and share your information. 

### Third Party Advertisers

We may allow other companies, called third-party ad servers or ad networks, to serve advertisements within the Websites. These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to send, directly to your browser, the advertisements and links that appear on the Websites. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. They may also use other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and to personalize the advertising content you see. You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers or ad networks for more information on their practices and for instructions on how to opt-out of certain practices. This Privacy Policy does not apply to them, and we cannot control their activities.

### Security

The security of your personal data is important to us. We have implemented and follows industry standard measures to protect against unauthorized access to and unlawful interception or processing of Personal data. We also protect account information by placing it in a secure database that is only accessible by certain qualified employees of Ivy Exec. When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card) on our registration or order forms, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet is 100% secure. While we strive to protect your Personal data, we cannot ensure or warranty the security of any such Personal data.

### Legal Disclaimer

We may disclose your Personal data when required by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary in order to conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on us. As such, we cannot ensure that your Personal data will not be disclosed to third parties. For example, we may be legally obligated to disclose information to the government or third parties under certain circumstances, or third parties may circumvent our security measures to unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications.

### Children’s Privacy

You must be at least 18 years old to register to use the Websites.

### Changes to this Privacy Policy

Ivy Exec reserves the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time in order that it might accurately reflect the regulatory environment and our data collection practices. By accessing the Websites at any time after such modifications, you are agreeing to such modifications. This Privacy Policy was last modified as May 25, 2017.

### California Privacy Rights

California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits users of the Websites who are California residents to request certain information regarding its disclosure of personal data to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an e-mail with "California Privacy Rights" in the heading to [privacy@ivyexec.com](mailto:privacy@ivyexec.com "privacy@ivyexec.com") or write us at:

Ivy Exec Privacy Rights   
49 W38th Street, Floor 12A  
New York, NY 10018
